easyfe.com 2017-10-27

# Easyfe - India's First Fully Automatic Mutual Fund Software. Online Mutual Fund Software for Independent Financial Advisors of India, Auto Upload of Mutual Fund Data from CAMS, Karvy, Franklin and Sundaram, Direct Upload from Registrar, Latest NAV, Software for Financial Advisors, Best Mutual Fund Software in India, Leading Mutual Fund Software in India, Free Software for Financial Advisors, Online Mutual Fund Portfolio, Mutual Fund Portfolio Viewer, Financial Software for ARN Holders of India

**Privacy Policy** :  **Last Updated: January 1, 2017**

This Privacy Policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) explains how easyfe.com(“easyfe ”, “us”, “our”, and “we”) uses your information and applies to all who use our Web site, mobile applications, electronic services, social networking sites, or any individuals, business partner-specific, merchant-specific, city-specific, or other area-specific Web sites we offer that link to or reference this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Site”) and when you receive electronic communications from us.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and review it periodically for the latest information about our privacy practices.  **By using this site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the practices describes in this Privacy Policy, please do not provide us with your personal information or interact with the Site.**

We will routinely update this Privacy Policy to clarify our practices and to reflect new or different privacy practices, such as when we add new services, functionality or features to the Site. If we make any material changes we will notify you by means of notification on the Site at the time of the change becoming effective. You can determine when this Privacy Policy was last revised by referring to the date it was “Last Updated” above.

**Information Collected by easyfe.com**

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website or mobile application. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We collect the following types of information from our easyfe.com users:

**Information You Provide to Us:**

We receive and store any information you enter on our website, uploaded through our mobile application or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.

Registration: In order for you to use easyfe.com services you may have to complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require select personal information.

User Profile: To allow you to express yourself beyond just the information collected during registration, we enable you to provide additional information. As indicated below, in the section titled "Sharing Your Information".

**Automatic Information:**

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. easyfe.com and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain "traffic data" on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, rasyfe.com cookie information, and the page you requested. easyfe.com uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website.

easyfe.com may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed. In connection with your use of mobile application products by Easyfe.com, location data may be transmitted and collected by requests for images you upload. You can disallow said location data transmission and collection by disabling location data services globally from the system settings of your mobile device. 

**User Media Privacy**

Any photograph or video uploaded to easyfe.com by the User (“User Media”) is subject to the Terms of Use. Despite the fact that by uploading content to easyfe.com, the User grants easyfe.com a worldwide, non-exclusive license to use the content, easyfe.com agrees not to distribute or otherwise make the same available except with your prior express consent.

Should you post your User Media to a third-party service, the privacy of that User Media will be governed by the third-party service’s Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.

**Text Communications**

easyfe.com is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your information to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the "Sharing Your Information" section below. easyfe.com may send out Push Notifications with easyfe.com- related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions. You may also receive notifications from easyfe.com, which inform you of actions (SIP date reminders) that have been performed on the site. If you do not want to receive Push Notifications from us, please visit the Notification Preferences section of your Mobile Device and disable Notifications. However, please note that in all cases you will continue to receive all system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and legal notices (e.g. updates to our policies) from us.

**Keeping Information Secure**

Your easyfe.com account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. Protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer.

Only employees who need personal information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices.

**Cookies**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. easyfe.com cookies do not collect personal information.

The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of easyfe.com's coolest features.

**Sharing Your Information**

Because easyfe.com will neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below.

easyfe.com Personnel: easyfe.com personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of Easyfe.com business.

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if easyfe.com, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that are transferred. 

Protection of easyfe.com and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of easyfe.com, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

easyfe.com Partners and Sponsors. Some easyfe.com products and services are offered to users in conjunction with a non-affiliated partner or sponsor. To provide users some of these products and services, the partner may need to collect and maintain personal information. easyfe.com will share non-identifying and aggregate information (except as described above), but not personal information, with such partners in order to administer the co-branded products or services offered.

**THIRD PARTY LINKS**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our website nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link or go from our web site to another web site, including those that have a link on our website, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Conditions of Use**

If you decide to visit easyfe.com website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of Ontario law.

**Effective Date of this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 1, 2017.

**Questions**

If you have questions about our sharing practices or your rights under Ontario, please write contact us at info@easyfe.com or contact us using the general communication page on the Site.
